(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
HOT LIMIT
妖精たちが 夏を刺激する
Fairies are stimulating the summer
生足 魅惑の マーメイド
Bare legs, a captivating mermaid
出すとこ出して たわわになったら
Showing what should be shown, and when it's ripened
本物の恋は やれ 爽快っ
A real love is, oh, so refreshing!
ごまかしきかない 薄着の曲線は
Can't hide them, the curves in light clothing
確信犯の しなやかな STYLE
A deliberate, supple STYLE
耐水性の 気持ちに切り替わる
Switching to a water-resistant feeling
瞬間の眩しさは いかがなもの
How about the dazzling brilliance of the moment?
ココロまで脱がされる
Being stripped down to the heart
熱い風の誘惑に
By the temptation of the hot wind
負けちゃって構わないから
It's okay to lose to it, because
真夏は 不祥事も キミ次第で
In midsummer, even scandals depend on you
妖精たちが 夏を刺激する
Fairies are stimulating the summer
生足 魅惑の マーメイド
Bare legs, a captivating mermaid
出すとこ出して たわわになったら
Showing what should be shown, and when it's ripened
本物の恋が でき爽快っ
A real love is formed, so refreshing!
キミじゃなくても バテキミにもなるよ
Even if it's not you, I'll get exhausted too
暑いばかりの 街は憂鬱で
The city that's only hot is depressing
スキを見せたら 不意に耳に入る
If I show a gap, I suddenly hear
寒いギャグなんかで 涼みたくない
I don't want to cool down with some bad joke
むせ返る 熱帯夜を
A sweltering tropical night
彩る 花火のように
Like fireworks coloring the sky
打ち上げて散る 想いなら
If these are feelings that shoot up and scatter
このまま抱き合って 焦がれるまで
Let's keep hugging like this until we're scorched
妖精たちが 夏をしたくなる
Fairies make me want to do summer
熱い欲望は トルネイド
Hot desires are a TORNADO
出すもの出して 素直になりたい
Letting it all out, I want to be honest
キミと僕となら IT'S ALL RIGHT
If it's you and me, IT'S ALL RIGHT
皆さん、今日は私の5周年ライブに見に来てくれてありがとうございます！
Everyone, thank you so much for coming to see my 5th-anniversary live today!
なんと、あん肝も一緒に踊ってくれてるよ！
Look, Ankimo is also dancing along!
わあー！盛り上がれー！
Wow! Let's get hyped!
はい！
Hai!
爽快の 伸びるの海じゃ
In the refreshing, stretching sea
感じなくなってる キミを
You, who have stopped feeling
冷えたワインの 口づけで
With the kiss of chilled wine
酔わせて 溶かして 差し上げましょう
I'll let you get drunk and melt you down
妖精たちが 夏を刺激する
Fairies are stimulating the summer
生足 へそ出し マーメイド
Bare legs, midriff-baring mermaid
恋に かまけて お留守になるのも
Being so preoccupied with love that you're absent-minded
ダイスケ的にも オールオッケー!
Even for Daisuke, it's all okay!
妖精夏を ドレスと したくなる
Wanting to make the fairy summer into a dress
独り寝の夜に YOU CAN SAY GOOD-BYE
To the nights sleeping alone, YOU CAN SAY GOOD-BYE
奥のほうまで 乾く間ないほど
To the point where there's no time to dry inside
本物の恋を しませんか
Won't you have a real love?
はい！というわけで、5周年ライブみんな
Yes! And so, everyone, for the 5th-anniversary live,
見に来てくれてありがとう！
thank you so much for coming to see it!
最初からいっぱい踊っちゃったよ。ありがとう。
I've been dancing a lot right from the start. Thank you.
お水を飲みながら、ちょっとお話を
I'm going to talk a bit while
しようかなと思います。お水はあっちだ。
I drink some water. The water is over there.
あ、お水だ、ありがとう。ありがとうございます。
Ah, water. Thank you. Thank you very much.
なんであん肝なの？でも可愛いけど。
Why is it Ankimo? It's cute though.
可愛いだろ？可愛いだろ？
Cute, isn't it? Cute, isn't it?
というわけで、あん肝の新衣装をね、ゲットしまして。
So, Ankimo got a new outfit.
ま、今日だけの新衣装なんですけど。
Well, it's a new outfit just for today.
後ろにもあん肝がいるっていう。
And there's another Ankimo in the back.
あん肝もね、増えるものだからしょうがない。ね？
Ankimo increases in number, so it can't be helped. Right?
そして今回はですね、ときのそら5周年記念ということで、
And this time, as it's Tokino Sora's 5th anniversary,
こちらのハッシュタグでつぶやいていただけると、
if you could use this hashtag to tweet about it,
嬉しいです！
I'd be very happy!
あ、可愛い。可愛いよね、可愛いよね、あん肝。
Ah, cute. It's cute, isn't it? Ankimo is cute.
ゲストにはね、0期生のみんなも後で登場するので、
As for guests, all the members of Generation 0 will appear later,
ぜひぜひよろしくお願いします。
so please look forward to it.
今回もね、まあ、知ってる人は知ってるかもしれないんですが、
Also, as some of you might already know,
告知もあるので、よろしくお願いいたしますね。
there are some announcements, so please stay tuned for those.
というわけで、一曲目踊ったばかりなんですけど、
So, even though I just finished dancing the first song,
早速歌っていこうと思います！いってきます！
I'm going to start singing right away! Here I go!
わぁーい！見てください、こちらですね。
Yay! Look at this.
初めてのワンマンライブ『Dream!』でね、着ました
This is the outfit that I wore for my
『Dream!』の衣装なんですけども。
very first solo live, 'Dream!'.
こちらで今回の曲、歌っていこうと思います。次の曲はですね、
I'm going to sing the next songs in this outfit. The next songs are
私のカバーアルバムの中からカバーさせていただいた曲を
from my cover album; I'd like you to listen to
2曲連続で聴いていただけたらと思います。それではいきましょう。
two songs in a row that I've covered. Here we go.
続いての曲は...『嘘』。
The next song is... 'Uso' (Lies).
嘘
Lies
作詞：マオ 作曲：ゆうや
Lyrics: Mao, Composition: Yuuya
あの日見た空　茜色の空を
The sky we saw that day, that madder-red sky...
ねえ　君は覚えていますか
Hey, do you remember it?
約束　初夏の風に消えた
Our promise vanished in the early summer breeze,
二人寄り添って
as we huddled together.
無理な笑顔の裏
Behind a forced smile,
伸びた影をかくまう
I hide the lengthening shadow.
だから　気づかぬふり
So, pretending not to notice,
再生を選んだ
I chose to start over.
テーブルの上の　震えない知らせ
On top of the table, a notification that doesn't vibrate,
待ち続けて
I keep waiting for it.
空白の夜も　来るはずのない朝も
The empty nights, and the mornings that will never come—
全部わかってたんだ
I knew it all.
あの日見た空　茜色の空を
The sky we saw that day, that madder-red sky...
ねえ　君は忘れたのでしょう
Hey, you've forgotten it, haven't you?
約束　初夏の風に消えた
Our promise vanished in the early summer breeze;
二人戻れない
we can't go back.
音も色も温度も
Sounds, colors, and temperature...
半分になった　この部屋
everything is halved in this room.
今日も散らかしては
Tidying up today too...
揺れ　疲れ　眠る
I sway, grow tired, and fall asleep.
揺らした気持ちは言いたいほど
The feelings I shook were almost too much to say
だから僕らサヨナラ
And so, we say goodbye
いつかまたねと手を振りあったけど
We waved and said "see you again sometime"
もう会うことはないのでしょう
But we likely won't ever meet again
最後の嘘は優しい嘘でした
That final lie was a kind one
忘れないあの日見た空
I won't forget the sky I saw that day
茜色の空を
That madder-red sky
ねぇいつか思い出すでしょう
Hey, you'll remember it eventually, won't you?
果たせなかった約束を抱いて
Embracing the promises we couldn't keep
二人歩き出す
The two of us start walking
God knows...
作詞：畑 亜貴　作曲：神前 暁
Lyrics: Aki Hata  Composition: Satoru Kosaki
乾いた心で駆け抜ける
Running through with a parched heart
ごめんね何もできなくて
I'm sorry I couldn't do anything
痛みを分かち合うことさえ
Even sharing the pain
あなたは許してくれない
Is something you won't allow
無垢に生きるため振り向かず
In order to live purely, without looking back
背中向けて去ってしまう
You turn your back and leave
on the lonely rail
私ついていくよ
I will follow you
どんな辛い世界の闇の中でさえ
No matter how bitter the darkness of this world
きっとあなたは輝いて
I'm sure you'll be shining
超える未来の果て
Beyond the end of the future
弱さゆえに魂壊されぬように
So your soul won't be broken by weakness
my way 重なるよ
my way, they overlap
今二人等しく
Now, the two of us equally
届けて熱くなる想いは
Deliver these feelings that are growing hot
現実溶かして彷徨う
They melt reality and wander
会いたい気持ちに理由はない
There's no reason for wanting to see you
あなたへ溢れだすラビリンス
A labyrinth overflowing towards you
せめて美しい夢だけを
Let's at least chase only beautiful dreams
描きながら追いかけよう
While painting them
for your lonely heart
やめて嘘はあなたらしくないよ
Stop it, lying isn't like you
目を見てこれからのことを話そう
Look into my eyes and let's talk about the future
私覚悟してる
I am prepared
暗い未来だって
Even for a dark future
強くなって運命変えられるかもね
If I get stronger, maybe I can change destiny
my wish かなえたいのに
Though I want to grant my wish
すべては
Everything is...
God knows...
あなたがいて私がいて
With you here and me here
他の人は消えてしまった
Everyone else has disappeared
淡い夢の美しさを描きながら
While painting the beauty of a faint dream
傷跡なぞる
Tracing the scars
だから私ついていくよ
So, I will follow you
どんな辛い世界の闇の中でさえ
No matter how bitter the darkness of this world
きっとあなたは輝いて
I'm sure you'll be shining
超える未来の果て
Beyond the end of the future
弱さゆえに魂壊されぬように
So your soul won't be broken by weakness
my way 重なるよ
my way, they overlap
...ありのままの二人で
...as we are, just the two of us
God bless...
はい、というわけで、2曲歌わせていただきました！
Yes, and with that, I've sung two songs!
そしてね、歌ってる間に演出が変わったの、すごいね！すごいね！
And also, while I was singing, the stage production changed.
Isn't that amazing? It's amazing!
これね、リハーサルで見たときに、あ、やっぱりスタッフさんは神なんだ、すごい、と思いながらね、リハーサルしてました。
When I saw this during rehearsal, I was rehearsing while
thinking, "Ah, the staff really are gods, this is incredible."
すごいよ！めちゃくちゃ嬉しい。
It's incredible! I'm so happy.
どう？衣装、ドレスになったよ！
How is it? My outfit turned into a dress!
イェーイ！
Yay!
というわけでね、あの、いつもの衣装、そしてドリーム衣装、そして一番新しくなった衣装ということで、今まで5周年でね...
So, from my usual outfit, to the Dream outfit,
and now to this newest one, over these past 5 years...
できた衣装をね、どんどん早着替えをしてきてみました！
I tried doing quick costume changes with all the outfits I've made!
いかがだったでしょうか？
How did you like it?
そしてですね、なんと！なんと！なんと！今日は本日ニューアルバム『Sign』のリリース日でもあったんですよ！イェーイ！
And also, guess what! Guess what! Guess what!
Today is actually the release day of my new album "Sign"! Yay!
こちら！
Here it is!
じゃあ、これを引っ提げてのライブも楽しみだなあ。ふふっ。
I'm really looking forward to the live concert featuring these songs. *Chuckle*
というわけで、すごいね、なんか錚々たる方々に作っていただいた曲で、なんかたくさん聴いていただけてるみたいで、感謝でいっぱいです。ぜひぜひ皆さん楽しんで聴いてください。
So, it's amazing. I'm full of gratitude because the songs were
created by such an illustrious group of people, and it seems like
many people are listening to them. Please, everyone, enjoy listening.
そして！
And!
こちら！リリースイベント、バーチャルお話会というのもね、開催しますので、よろしくお願いします。
This! We'll also be holding a release event, a virtual talk
session, so please look forward to it.
1回目の締め切りはなんと今日なんですけど、まあまあまあ、その、その次がね、まだまだ締め切りまでありますので、ぜひぜひみんな...
The deadline for the first round is actually today, but well,
the next one still has some time before the deadline, so I'd be very happy...
見てもらえると嬉しいな。イベントの詳細チェックしてね！
...if everyone could check it out. Check the event details!
にゅう〜。
Nyuu~
やあ、なんかもう、すでに感無量なんだけど。
Yeah, I'm already feeling completely overwhelmed with emotion.
ちょっと次の曲もね、歌っていきたいなとは思います。
I'd like to sing the next song now.
お水を飲んでくるね。
I'm going to go drink some water.
お水を飲んできました！
I've finished drinking my water!
じゃ、次の曲からは、えー、アルバムの曲を初めてここで披露したいなと思っているので、ぜひぜひそちらの方、聴いていただけたら嬉しいです。
Now, from the next song onwards, I'll be performing songs
from the album for the first time here, so I'd be very
happy if you could listen to them.
それでは聴いてください。アルバム『Sign』から、『ピッとして！マーマレード』！
Then, please listen. From the album "Sign", "Bitto Shite! Marmalade"!
こんなにこんなに叶えたいんだ
I want it to come true this much, this much
強く願って願うだけ夢になった
Simply wishing and wishing strongly, it became a dream
そうだから しっかりピッとしてマーマレード
That's why, pull yourself together, Marmalade!
私がんばるよ がんばるからね
I'll do my best, I really will!
よっしゃ Get up, Stand up, Run up, Grow up!
Alright! Get up, Stand up, Run up, Grow up!
時に真面目で 時にちゃらけて
Sometimes serious, sometimes playful
時に凛々しく
Sometimes dignified
コロコロ変わる そら模様みたい
Changing constantly, like the state of the sky
どれもちゃんとそらだし
Every version is truly Sora
There's no place 私と君の
There's no place. Between you and me
やり取りが線になる
Our interactions become a line
素敵 ロマンチックで ドラマチック
Wonderful, romantic and dramatic
星座になって そして歌になる
Becoming a constellation, and then becoming a song
見せかけって言えるほど たくましく
Resilient enough to call it a facade
できてないかもしれない
I might not be there yet
正々堂々トライ・アンド・エラーって感じが
That feeling of fair-and-square trial and error
あいまいみーまい
Is "I, my, me, mine"
ねえ、これが私でいいから
Hey, because this version of me is just fine
いいでしょ ちょっとやそっとじゃ揺るがないの
It's okay, right? It won't be shaken by just a little
こんくらい笑ったら 笑えちゃうの
If you laugh this much, you really can laugh
笑えたら 次に行こう
Once you laugh, let's move on to the next
気づいてる ちょっと成長してるよ
I've noticed, I'm growing a little
キュートにキュートに甘いだけじゃなくて
Not just cute, cute, and sweet
ほんのりほろほろ苦いの
But a little bit bittersweet too
だって ここまでピッとしてマーマレード
Because, pull yourself together up to this point, Marmalade!
君に会えるまで 次は何にしよう
Until I can see you, what should I do next?
よっしゃ Get up, Stand up, Run up, Grow up!
Alright! Get up, Stand up, Run up, Grow up!
だいぶ凝って 真心込めて 届けたいんだもん
I've put a lot of effort into it, with all my heart, because I want to deliver it.
一期一会 かもしれないけど
It might be a once-in-a-lifetime encounter, but...
繋がれ そばみたく
Connect, as if staying by your side.
どんな服着て 街に出よう
What kind of clothes should I wear to go out?
どんな髪型を試そう
What kind of hairstyle should I try?
きっと一つ一つ 君に見てほしいから
Because I want you to see every little thing.
本当だよ 君はどうだろう
It's true, I wonder how it is for you?
想いがいっぱい いっぱい 連なって
Feelings are piling up, piling up, linking together.
奇跡がいっぱい いっぱい 起きちゃって
Miracles are happening, happening, more and more.
見たことない 景色になって
Turning into a sight I've never seen before.
君と私が作った 景色だよ
It's the scenery that you and I made together.
とってもとっても 嬉しいんだ
I'm so, so happy.
だからね 本当に本当に ありがとうだ
So, really, really, thank you.
君がくれる その声で ママレード
With that voice you give me, Marmalade.
どんな色にでも なれる個性に
In a personality that can become any color.
溶かすメロディや
A melting melody and...
ちょっぴり ゆるリズムで
...with a slightly loose rhythm.
楽しさ 混ぜて 沸かせていく
...mix in the fun and let it boil.
根っから私は私でいたい
I want to be myself from the bottom of my heart.
こんなにこんなに 叶えたくて
Wanting to make it come true so, so much.
強く願って 願うだけ 夢になって
Wishing strongly, just by wishing it becomes a dream.
なったからね 諦めるはずない
And since it has, there's no way I'll give up.
そのステージは きっとそこにある
That stage is surely right there.
一緒に一緒に 目指したいの
I want to aim for it together, together.
景色を一緒に 一緒に作りたいの
I want to create the scenery together, together.
鼓動高く しっかり ピットしてママレード
Heart beating fast, firmly Pit-te! Marmalade.
私頑張るよ 頑張るからね
I'll do my best, I'll really do my best.
grow up! run up! stand up! get up!
本当にありがとう
Thank you so much.
ぜんぶ ピットして ママレード
Everything, Pit-te! Marmalade.
みんながこうやってコメントを繋いでくれたから、私は5年間ここに立っていられるよ。本当にありがとう！
Because everyone connected their comments like this, I've been able to stand here for five years. Thank you so much!
はい！ というわけで、
Yes! So,
ピットして！マーマレード、初めて披露しました！
I performed "Pit-te! Marmalade" for the first time!
イェーイ！ イェーイ！
Yay! Yay!
駆け出しちゃってごめんなさい...
Sorry for running off...
ごめんなさい、走りたくなっちゃって
Sorry, I just felt like running.
そして、ここでね、一発表がある。今日は駆け足なんだ。
And now, I have an announcement. Today is a bit of a rush.
発表することが多いんだ。
There are many things to announce.
ということで、活動5周年記念企画のひとつ、soraSongグランプリっていうのがあったんですけど、みなさん覚えてますかね？
So, one of the 5th anniversary projects, the "soraSong Grand Prix" - do you all remember it?
そらともさんからオリジナル曲をね募集させていただくっていうやつなんですけど、なんとね、噂によると50曲以上集まったらしいんですよ。
It was where we asked Soratomo for original songs, and believe it or not, I heard over 50 songs were submitted!
ありがとうございます。ありがとうございます。
Thank you. Thank you.
そしてですね、その中の一曲を実は、えー、最優秀ということで選ばせていただきました。
And from those, I've actually chosen one song as the Grand Prize winner.
今回選ばせていただいた曲がですね、じゃじゃーん！
The song I chose is... ta-da!
soraSongグランプリ 優勝作品決定！
soraSong Grand Prix Winner Decided!
え、komoさんという方の『ケ・セラ・ソラ！』という曲をですね、選ばせていただきました。
I've chosen the song "Que Sera Sora!" by someone named komo.
素敵な曲ありがとうございます。
Thank you for the wonderful song.
そしてなんと今日、初披露、ここで、え、ワンコーラスではあるんですけど、
And today, for the first time, right here - although it's only one chorus -
最優秀作品のケ・セラ・ソラをですね、歌っちゃいたいなと思います！
I'm going to sing the Grand Prize winner, "Que Sera Sora"!
本当に初披露です。
It's truly the first time.
みなさんぜひぜひ、初めての曲聴いていってください。
Everyone, please listen to this new song.
それではいきますかね？
Shall we start?
それでは聴いてください。ケ・セラ・ソラ！
Please listen: "Que Sera Sora!"
せーの！ ケ・セラ・ソラ！
One, two! Que Sera Sora!
おはよう 朝日に今日もご挨拶
Good morning, greeting the morning sun again today.
え、あれ、うそ、もうこんな時間？
Wait, no way, is it already this time?
ここから予定あるのに すぐに支度をしなきゃ
I have plans from now, I have to get ready quickly.
急いで扉開けて気づく
I rush out the door and realize...
お財布ない！ ここどこ？ 待って、定期も！
"My wallet is gone! Where am I? Wait, my pass too!"
トラブルばっか 転んで起きての
Nothing but trouble, falling and getting back up...
毎日で
In our daily lives,
何でも思い通りとか
not everything goes exactly as planned,
そんな美味しい話はないけど
there aren't many stories that easy, but
心の曇り空を晴らす合言葉
when you chant the secret phrase
唱えたらね ほら 快晴でしょ
to clear the cloudy skies in your heart, look, it's a clear day!
ずっとみんなに届けたい
I want to keep delivering to everyone
歌もダンスも元気も
my songs, my dance, and my energy.
きっと同じ空の下
Surely, under the same sky,
笑顔も分け合えるよ
we can share our smiles too.
ちょっと疲れちゃうときも
Even when you're a little tired,
涙が出そうなときも
or when you're about to cry,
いつもの魔法の言葉 今日も
today too, the usual magic words are:
ケ・セラ・ソラの空！
Que Sera Sora's sky!
時にアイをソライ
Sometimes, let love soar through the sky
キミのソラをオドレ
Dance in your own sky
Wanna be a Superstar
みんなクラップ！
Everyone, clap!
呼吸(ログ)を更新しなきゃ
I have to update my logs (breath)
昨日の夢は過ぎ去ってんだのさ
Yesterday's dreams have already passed by
奇跡に替えたあの時だってさ
Even those moments that turned into miracles
越えて 越えて 越えて 行くんだ
I'll keep on crossing, crossing, crossing over them
First MV 重ねた Stage
Accumulating stages since the first MV
Code name は 17 My offset
Code name is 17, My offset
ゼロの Dream に果てないで
Don't let the dream from zero come to an end
Come on, Follow! Every time, Every day, 止まらねーぞ！
Come on, Follow! Every time, Every day, I'm not stopping!
ブレーキがきかなかったあの日 アタシと
That day when the brakes didn't work, with me
ブレずと一緒にいて頂戴
Please stay with me without wavering
あなただけの Wanna be a Superstar
A "Wanna be a Superstar" just for you
Wanna wanna wanna wanna wanna be a Superstar!
時にアイをソライ
Sometimes, let love soar through the sky
キミのソラをオドレ
Dance in your own sky
煌き放て大きく舞われ
Release your sparkle and dance grandly
虹色の輪 Our world
A rainbow-colored ring, our world
悔しい日もあったね
There were days of frustration, weren't there?
一緒に涙したね
We shed tears together, didn't we?
あの日があるから今がある
Because of those days, we have today
ついてきて！ OK?
Follow me! OK?
時にアイをソライ
Sometimes, let love soar through the sky
キミのソラをオドレと共に Let's go!
Together, let's dance in your sky! Let's go!
私達の未来は蒼の層
Our future is a layer of blue
絶滅危惧のフェーズへ暴走中
Racing towards an endangered phase
誰が進んだ？拒んでる暇はないんだ
Who moved forward? There's no time to refuse
やるんだ！やろうぜ！あたししかないんだ！
Do it! Let's do it! It has to be me!
恐れる気持ちは皆同じだ
Everyone feels fear the same way
ひるんで引き返すのはあたしもだ
I'm also one to flinch and turn back
でもそんな時こその合言葉
But that's exactly when we need the secret phrase
Every time, Every day, 止まらねーぞ！
Every time, Every day, I'm not stopping!
アイをカラー 鮮やかにしてあげるわ
I'll make the color of love vivid for you
輝く永遠のエキシビション
A sparkling, eternal exhibition
あなただけの Wanna be a Superstar
A "Wanna be a Superstar" just for you
Wanna wanna wanna wanna wanna be a Superstar!
時にアイをソライ
Sometimes, let love soar through the sky
キミのソラをオドレ
Dance in your own sky
ぎゅっと抱き寄せ夢を奏でて
Hold me tight and play the melody of dreams
虹色の輪 Our world
A rainbow-colored ring, our world
無限に夢を発信
Broadcasting dreams infinitely
キミがいれば安心
I feel safe as long as you're here
キミと会えたからソラがある
Because I met you, the sky exists
ありがとう！ ありがとう！
Thank you! Thank you!
ずっとアイをソライ
Always let love soar through the sky
ずっとソラをオドレと共に Let's go!
Always dance in the sky together! Let's go!
みんなクラップ！
Everyone, clap!
クラップ！ クラップ！ クラップ！
Clap! Clap! Clap!
宇宙の果ての正解をキミと探し当てたい
I want to find the answer at the edge of the universe with you
最初の着陸はキミと挑みたい
I want to challenge the first landing with you
ひとつずつ思い出を作って
Creating memories one by one
ひとつずつ今を積み重ねて
Accumulating moments one by one
同じ過去 同じ今
The same past, the same present
同じ未来 享受できるだろう
We'll be able to enjoy the same future
時にアイをソライ
Sometimes, let love soar through the sky
キミのソラをオドレ
Dance in your own sky
煌き放て大きく舞われ
Release your sparkle and dance grandly
虹色の輪 Our world
A rainbow-colored ring, our world
悔しい日もあったね
There were days of frustration, weren't there?
一緒に涙したね
We shed tears together, didn't we?
...に時間をね
...to time.
あの日があるから今がある
Because of that day, I am here today.
ついてきて！
Come with me!
Okay!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
大好きだよ！
I love you all!
Okay!
ときに愛をよこせ　君の空を
Sometimes give me your love, your sky.
ずっと愛を紡ぐ　ずっと空を
I'll keep spinning love, across the sky.
ときに愛をよこせ　君の空を
Sometimes give me your love, your sky.
空がたもつまた Let's go!
The sky remains, so let's go!
Ah ah ah- Ah ah ah-
Wow wow wow- Wow wow wow-
Let's go!
はい！ということで、空ソングの『ケ・セラ・ソナタ』と
Yes! So, that was the Sora-song 'Que Sera Sonata' and
えー、新録曲『そらのとき』でした！どうだった？
uh, the newly recorded song 'Sora no Toki'! How was it?
ときに愛をちょうだい！はい！
Give me love sometimes! Yes!
はい！ということで、いやー、楽しかったかな、みんな！
Yes! So, was it fun, everyone?!
今回はね、上がる曲をいっぱい歌いたいなと思って
This time, I wanted to sing a lot of upbeat songs.
今、ちょっと喋りながら若干後悔をしている自分がいる...
Right now, as I'm talking, a part of me is slightly regretting it...
すごい息が切れてるなーと思っているね。
I'm thinking, 'Wow, I'm really out of breath.'
ねー。でもみんなが楽しそうで、すごく嬉しい！
Right? But you all look so happy, and that makes me so glad!
やったー！
Hooray!
みんなみんな、ぜひぜひいっぱい聴いて楽しんでね！
Everyone, please listen to it a lot and enjoy!
いぇーい！
Yay!
はい、というわけで、この後はなんと
Alright, and up next...
ゲストパートだよ！
...is the guest part!
私もお着替えしてこなくちゃ！
I have to go change too!
同じ未来　指先で描きたい　あの夢手にしたい
The same future, I want to draw it with my fingertips, I want to grasp that dream.
それぞれ違った心で
With our own different hearts,
走れもっと！
Run even more!
Shiny Smily Story 2022 ver.
どこを見ても真っ暗な場所に　芽生えていた
In a place where it was pitch black no matter where you looked, it had sprouted.
こんな小さな希望に　瞳奪われた
By such a small hope, my eyes were captivated.
不安で揺れる心を　うまくチューニングして
Tuning my heart that trembles with anxiety well,
こんな小さな勇気も　振り絞って行こう
let's squeeze out even this tiny bit of courage and go.
あきらめの文字　デリートして進む
Deleting the word 'giving up' as I move forward.
苦しい時も　もう私は一人じゃないから
Even in painful times, I'm not alone anymore.
だからもっと夢追いかけたい　ワクワク止まらない
So I want to chase my dreams even more, the excitement won't stop.
想像を超えてく世界　見せてあげる
I'll show you a world that exceeds your imagination.
アクセスしてみたい　後悔なんてさせない
I want to try accessing it, I won't let you regret it.
それぞれ違った心で
With our own different hearts,
走れもっと！
Run even more!
理想の空に輝く　眩しい想いは
The dazzling thoughts shining in the ideal sky,
見たこともない光を　リアルに届けるよ
will deliver a light you've never seen before, for real.
いつも聴こえるエールは　ここにキャプチャして
The cheers I always hear, I'll capture them here,
また新しい光を　探したくなるよ
and I'll want to search for new light again.
君の笑顔は　保存して進む
Saving your smile as I move forward.
悲しい時に見返すよ　力が湧くから
I'll look back at it when I'm sad, because it gives me strength.
胸を張って夢追いかけたい　奇跡はストーリー
I want to chase my dreams with pride, miracles are a story.
一緒に作ろう　終わらない夢
Let's create it together, an unending dream.
誰一人欠かせない　愛が待ったこの世界
No one is replaceable in this world where love waited.
それぞれ違った心で
Color it with your own different hearts!
彩って！
Color it!
動き出した
Moving forward
信じ続けたい
I want to keep believing
終わらない世界に
In this endless world
あふれ出した
Overflowing
笑顔たち
Smiles
憧れの舞台立ちたい
I want to stand on the stage I've dreamed of
まぶしく輝きたい
I want to shine brilliantly
ときに涙して
Sometimes shedding tears
また笑いあいたい
I want to laugh together again
同じ未来を見たい
I want to see the same future
あの夢手に入れたい
I want to grasp that dream
目指そう 奇跡の 一歩を
Let's aim for that miracle step
いききなして 夢追いかけたい
I want to keep living and chasing dreams
ワクワク止まらない
The excitement won't stop
想像を超えてく世界見せてあげる
I'll show you a world that exceeds your imagination
アクセスしてみない？
Won't you try to access it?
後悔なんてここにない
There are no regrets here
それぞれ違ったコトバで作るわ
We'll create it with our own different words
わー！
Whoo!
さあ！ということで今回のスペシャルゲストは！
Now! With that being said, today's special guests are!
はい！0期生のみんなだよー！
Yes! Everyone from Generation 0!
イエーイ！おめでとう！5周年おめでとう！
Yay! Congratulations! Congratulations on your 5th anniversary!
いや、楽しかったね。
Man, that was fun.
楽しかったー！
It was fun!
エモすぎて。感極まっちゃうよ。
It's so emotional. I'm getting overwhelmed.
こうやってね、頑張ったよ。みんなで頑張った。
We worked hard like this. Everyone worked hard together.
あのサードフェスの振り付けでね、やりました。
We did it with the choreography from the 3rd Fes.
ワキワキと。ワキワキとね。
Wakiwaki. Wakiwaki, right.
さあ、もう6年目か。
Now, the 6th year is starting.
そうだよ。今日から6年目！すごいなー！
That's right. The 6th year starting today! That's amazing!
早い！なんかもう5年もやったのかっていう感覚あるわ。
So fast! I feel like, "I've already been doing this for 5 years?"
もう5年です。
It's already been 5 years.
でも、うん。何気にこの記念枠とかで0期生集まるのは初めて。
But, yeah. Actually, it's the first time Generation 0 has gathered like this for an anniversary stream.
初めて！そうなのー！
The first time! Is that so!
確かに、なかなが集まんないね。
True, we don't gather very often.
なんかもうホロライブはまったばかりの人はなんだこの面子って思ってるかもしれない。
People who just recently got into Hololive might be thinking, "Who are these people?"
確かに。元祖を知らないのかもね。
True. They might not know the originals.
なんだこれ！言われてたもんね、元祖とかね。
"What's this!" We used to be called the originals and such.
元祖！レジェンド！
Originals! Legends!
あー。集まってこれたね。0期生とかのみんなで。
Ah. We were able to gather. Everyone from Generation 0 and all.
そう、あの、だってね。ファーストフェスか。ファーストフェスで一応5人で一緒にステージ立ったんだけど。
Right, because, well. Was it the 1st Fes? We did stand on stage together as five at the 1st Fes.
そうそう。そん時はまだ0期生って名前が浸透してなくて。
Yeah, yeah. At that time, the name "Generation 0" hadn't really caught on yet.
確かに。それぞれソロ組みたいな。そう、デビュー組だった。
True. We were like individual soloists. Right, the debut group.
特になんか、あんまりなんかしかもさ、名前が本当に色々あったから、派閥が。
Especially, and also, there were really a lot of different names, like factions.
0期生、元祖、ソロ組って。
Generation 0, originals, solo group.
どれが合ってるんだろう、みたいな。
Like, "Which one is correct?"
私たちなんか、井の中組だったかも。
We might have been the "Inonaka group" or something.
そうだね。色んな時代を経て。
That's right. Going through various eras.
こうしてここにみんな集まって、0期生ってなって集まってるのは。
Everyone gathering here like this, gathering as Generation 0...
イエーイ！
Yay!
いや今日はね、あのね、節目っていうこともありまして。
Well today, you see, it being a milestone...
はい。ずっとね、なんか最初から一緒に頑張ってきたメンバーをゲストに呼びたーいっていうので。
Yes. Because I wanted to invite the members who have worked hard together with me from the very beginning as guests.
うん。みんなでやっぱり私たちの曲で、SSSで、ステージ立ちたいなーと思ってやりました。
Yeah. I thought I really wanted us all to stand on stage together with our song, SSS.
嬉しい。
So happy.
でも2022年バージョン。
But it was the 2022 version.
そうだよ。めっちゃよかった。映像もすごかった。
That's right. It was so good. The visuals were amazing too.
エモさがね、さらにアップしてね。
The emotional feeling was even higher, right.
よかった。ではみんなで、こういうアイドルポーズみんな決めちゃう感じ。
Glad to hear it. Well then, let's all strike some idol poses together.
イエーイ！
Yay!
はい。写真いっぱい撮ってー。
Yes. Take lots of pictures!
撮って撮ってー。珍しいぞー。
Take 'em, take 'em. This is rare!
本当に珍しい。
Truly rare.
次は猫耳ポーズ、みんなでポンってしよう。せーの！
Next is cat ears pose, let's all go "pon". Ready, go!
はにゃ。
Hanya.
パシャ、パシャ。写真が撮れたよ。
Click, click. We got the pictures.
こういうやつら。
These kinds of guys.
次は、次は。次は何がいいかな。
Next, next. What should we do next?
セクシーなポーズ。3、2、1、はい！
A sexy pose. 3, 2, 1, go!
大体みんな一緒。
Everyone's mostly doing the same thing.
アダッチューの。アハハ。
Adacchuu style. Ahaha.
大体宝鐘マリンになるわ。
We mostly end up like Houshou Marine.
確かに。ポーズが同じになっちゃうんだよね、なんだかんだ。
True. The poses end up being the same after all.
宝鐘マリンです。
I'm Houshou Marine.
はい、次は次はー。
Okay, next, next...
何しに行くの、次？
What are we doing next?
ありさ、まだ、まだ時間あるからさ
Wait, we still have time.
あずきちゃん、あずきちゃん、なんか...
AZKi-chan, AZKi-chan, how about...
え、何？
Eh, what?
何でもいいよ、ほら
Anything is fine, look.
ねえ、ちょっとみんな、まっすぐ並ぼうよ
Hey, let's all line up straight.
あ、縦に、縦に？
Ah, in a column? Vertically?
あ、じゃあじゃあ、こう、こう、このまま、このまま
Ah, then, like this, like this, just as we are.
あ、じゃあ、一番、一番前行くわ、私
Ah, then I'll go to the very front.
で、中腰になる、私がちょっと
And I'll crouch a bit.
おお、みんな見える？
Oh, can you all see?
あ、いいじゃん、これ
Ah, this is great!
いい感じ、いい感じ
Looking good, looking good.
小さいゆえに、小さいのになんで後ろなんだ、お前！
Being small... why are you in the back when you're small?!
これ、いいじゃないですか
This is pretty good, isn't it?
あ、いいよいいよ、いいよ
Ah, nice, nice, nice!
イェーイ！
Yay!
あ、これ、チューチュートレインできるんじゃない？
Ah, can't we do Choo Choo TRAIN with this?
そうそうそうそう
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
行くよ、せーの！
Here we go, one, two!
ぐるぐる、ぐるぐる
Spin, spin, spin, spin.
あ、きれい、きれい、きれい！
Ah, so beautiful, beautiful, beautiful!
いい感じ、これ、上手！
Looking good, we're good at this!
ウヒョーイ！
Wooohooo!
何これ、何の会、何の会、これ
What's this? What kind of gathering is this?
懐かしい、懐かしい、こんなこともやったな
How nostalgic, nostalgic. We used to do stuff like this.
やったね、やった。強固な、強固にされてる
We did it! We did it. Our bond is strengthened.
やばい、この5年でこんなこといっぱいしたな
Wow, we've done so many things like this in these 5 years.
そうだね、いろいろあったね、ねえ
Right, so much has happened.
はい、というわけで、そらちゃんが何か告知したいことがあると...
Alright, and with that, Sora-chan has something to announce...
あ、そうなんです、告知！
Ah, that's right, an announcement!
え、何、何ですか、何ですか？
Eh, what? What is it? What is it?
なんと今日はですね、今回5周年を記念して...
Well, today, to commemorate the 5th anniversary...
おお、グッズをご用意してあります！
Oh, we have some merchandise prepared!
イェーイ！
Yay!
画像、画像！
The image, show the image!
どれどれ、どれどれ？
Let's see, let's see.
はい、今回のグッズはこちらです！
Yes, here is the merchandise!
ああ、かわいい、かわいい！
Ah, so cute, so cute!
活動5周年記念ということでですね、この...
Since it's the 5th anniversary of my activities...
記念ボイス1種類と記念グッズ3種類をちょっとご用意しております
We've prepared one memorial voice and three memorial items.
わーい！
Yay!
1つずつ、ちょっと見ていこうかなと思います。まずは1つ目はこちら！
Let's take a look at them one by one. First, here's the first one!
お、お！
Oh, oh!
ランダムアクリルキーホルダー！
Random Acrylic Keyholder!
イェーイ！
Yay!
今回はですね、イラスト、いかき先生に描いていただきまして
This time, the illustration was drawn by Ikaki-sensei.
いかき先生、懐かしい！
Ikaki-sensei, how nostalgic!
あの、初期からずっと私の、ね、最初のなんか...
Um, they've been helping me since the very beginning...
お世話になった、お世話になった方なんですけど
They're someone who really looked after me back then.
その方にイラストを描いていただきました。どれも可愛いくて
I had them draw the illustrations. They're all so cute.
ぜひ、ぜひみんな見てもらえると嬉しいです！
I'd be so happy if everyone could take a look!
見て、可愛い！
Look, they're cute!
そして次が、こちら！
And next is this one!
お、Tシャツ！
Oh, a T-shirt!
ザリガニTシャツで、イラストはかせさんという方に描いていただきました
It's a crayfish T-shirt, and the illustration was by Kase-san.
ザリガニではない、ザリガニではない、これ、ザリガニじゃん！
It's not a crayfish... It's totally a crayfish!
でも、でも、おしゃれかもしれない
But, but it might actually be stylish.
おしゃれだよ、すごいおしゃれ。可愛い、かっこいい
It is stylish, very stylish. Cute and cool.
なんだ、どんぐりが3つ連なってるようにしか...
Wait, it just looks like three acorns lined up...
違う、あれは、違う、あれは顔と、胴体と...
No, those are... no, that's the face, the body, and...
尻尾。ハサミがハートになってて、ハサミ、ハサミなんだよ
The tail. The claws are shaped like hearts. They're claws!
あ、触角じゃないんだ、あれは。ハサミなんだ
Ah, those aren't antennae? They're claws.
どう見てもザリガニやろ！ お前ら毒されすぎだ！
No matter how you look at it, it's a crayfish! You're too biased!
だから、なんか、ちょっとおしゃれにしようかなと思って...
So, I thought I'd make it a little stylish...
おしゃれ、おしゃれです。夏休みの自由研究してる時に着たい
It is stylish. I'd wear it during my summer research project.
フォローしてるように見えてフォローしてない、それ！ 気にしないで、そらちゃん
You sound like you're helping but you're not! Don't mind her, Sora-chan.
はい、次。次行きます。次はこちらです！
Alright, next. Moving on. Here is the next one!
ああ、可愛い！ ぬんぬん、ぬんぬん、可愛い！
Ah, so cute! Nun-nun, Nun-nun, so cute!
可愛いでしょう。なんか、もふもふなものが作りたいなと思って...
It's cute, right? I wanted to make something fluffy...
いいじゃん。あれ？ もしかして、なんか見つけた様子？
It's nice. Wait, did you find something?
あれ？ もしかして、あんきも？！
Wait, could it be... Ankimo?!
うわー、いつの間にか出ている！ 可愛い、そらちゃん！
Whoa, he's out already! So cute, Sora-chan!
あ、ここには、ここには、なんかぬんぬん、ぬんぬん...
Ah, over here, over here, some Nun-nun, Nun-nun...
あんきもだ、あんきもが嫉妬してる！
It's Ankimo! Ankimo is jealous!
可愛い、あんきももいるよ。どっちも可愛いよ
So cute, Ankimo is here too. Both are cute.
浮いてる、ぬんぬん、浮いているけど、よろしくね！
Nun-nun is floating, but please take care of them!
そらちゃん、見て、買ってほしそうだよ、これ
Sora-chan, look, they look like they want to be bought.
マジ、あんきも欲しい、あんきも欲しい、あんきも欲しい！
Seriously, I want Ankimo, I want Ankimo, I want Ankimo!
大人気、みこち、ほら、あ、やった、くれた！
So popular! Mikochi, look, ah, nice, she gave it to me!
うわー、やったー！ うわー、見て、あんきも！
Whoa, yay! Whoa, look, Ankimo!
可愛い、今日の主役、ぬんぬん！
So cute, today's star, Nun-nun!
ぬんぬん！
Nun-nun!
遊びに来てくれよな！
Come visit us!
わーい！よしよしよしよし……
Yay! There, there, there...
どんどん、どんどんマスコットキャラが増えていく現象が起こっておりますが、とってもよろしくねということで。
The mascot characters just keep increasing, so please treat them well.
可愛い！絶対ゲットしたい！
So cute! I definitely want to get one!
そしてそして、これが全部合わさったものもありますね。ドン！
And then, we also have a set with everything included. Ta-da!
ドン！はい、こちらがですね……
Ta-da! Yes, this is...
あ、そうそう、このボイス単品っていうのもあります。
Oh right, you can also get the voices individually.
シチュエーションボイスですね。
They are situation voices.
やっぱり気になるからね。そ、それと、秋服のお買い物デート！
Because we're curious. Yes, that, and an autumn clothes shopping date!
お買い物！お買い物！
Shopping! Shopping!
シチュエーションボイスも、ええ、喋りましたのでぜひぜひよろしくお願いします。
I've recorded a situation voice, so please check it out.
はい！そしてフルセットがこちらです。
Yes! And here is the full set.
フルセットの特典としては、こちらのですね、描き下ろしのものに……
As for the full set bonus, this newly drawn illustration...
……ええ、箔押しのサインをつけてお送りしますので、よろしくお願いします。
...will come with a foil-stamped signature, so please look forward to it.
欲しい！欲しい！
I want it! I want it!
というわけで告知コーナーでございました。よろしくお願いします！
And that was the announcement corner. Please check them out!
みんなゲットしてくれよな！よろしく！
Everyone, please get them! Thanks!
ぬんぬんたちも出てきたからまたプリクラやるかい？
Since the Nunnuns are out, shall we do another photo booth pose?
やりたい！やりたい！
Let's do it! Let's do it!
どうやって撮ろうか、そしたら……
How should we take it then...
客席をさ、背景にしない？
Should we use the audience as the background?
あ、いいね！客席側に……
Oh, that's good! Towards the audience...
こうやってみんなでなんかよくあるやつ撮る？最後の……
Should we all take one of those common photos? For the finale...
あ！みんなで！ライブポーズ！
Oh! Everyone! Live pose!
あ、待って……
Oh, wait...
ここだ、ここだ。はい！
Here, here. Okay!
イエーイ！イエーイ！
Yay! Yay!
みんな見に来てくれてありがとう！
Thank you everyone for coming to see us!
すごいみんな振ってくれてる！イエーイ！イエーイ！
Wow, everyone is waving! Yay! Yay!
大はしゃぎ！大はしゃぎ！可愛い！
So much excitement! So much excitement! So cute!
ありがとう！イエーイ！
Thank you! Yay!
あんきもぷ！ボクぬんぬん……
Ankimo-p! I'm Nunnun...
ぬんぬん、ぬんぬん、ぬんぬん、ぬんぬん……
Nun-nun, nun-nun, nun-nun, nun-nun...
仲良くなってる、いつの間にか。いいな。なでなで。
They've become friends all of a sudden. That's nice. Pet me, pet me.
イエーイ！イエーイ！
Yay! Yay!
おやおやおやおや……
Oh my, oh my...
……と、そんなこと言ってる間に、もう時間が来てしまいました。
...and while we were doing that, it's already time to end.
早い！早い！
So fast! So fast!
みんなの方見て終わろうとしたら……そ、いいね！こっちでも写真みたいな感じで終わりましょうか。
If we were to end while looking at everyone... Yes, that's good! Let's end with a photo-like pose here too.
みんな見えてるし。そらちゃん目立つな……
Since everyone can see us. Sora-chan, you really stand out...
とりあえず消しなさんと……そこに……そこに……
For now, with Keshina-san... there... there...
やだやだ！離れたくない！離れたくないけど！
No, no! I don't want to leave! I don't want to leave, but!
はい！今日のスペシャルコラボ、0期生のみんなでした！ありがとう！
Yes! Today's special collab was the 0th generation members! Thank you!
ありがとう！バイバイ！
Thank you! Bye-bye!
はい、というわけで、ぬんぬんがまだ残ってる。ぬんぬんちゃんがここにいますが……
Okay, so, Nunnun is still here. Nunnun-chan is right here...
……本日はありがとうございます。
...thank you very much for today.
新曲などたくさん披露させていただいたり、0期生のみんなと一緒にライブをしたり、もう最高の5周年です。
Performing many new songs and having a live with all the 0th gen members, it's the best 5th anniversary.
5周年っていうのはなんか正直あまり実感がなくて……
To be honest, I didn't really have a sense of it being the 5th anniversary...
……こうしてみんながおめでとうってたくさんの人にこう見ていただけて、やっと今ちょっとちょっとずつ実感をしてきたなって感じがします。
...but seeing so many people saying congratulations, I'm finally starting to feel it little by little.
これからも秋にはですね、私もライブを控えておりまして、また頑張っていきたいなと思ってるんですが……
I have a live concert coming up this autumn, and I want to keep doing my best...
……これからもね、このあとも色々ありますから、5周年、ホロライブも5周年なので、どんどん頑張っていきたいなって思ってます。
...there's still more to come, and since it's the 5th anniversary for Hololive too, I want to keep pushing forward.
ええ、そうですね、なんかこうしてみんながね、パチパチパチパチってしてる中でこうね……
Yes, well, with everyone clapping like this...
……最初は歌うのも緊張してたんですけど、今ではみんなのコメントのおかげで楽しく歌うことができています。
...I used to be nervous about singing, but now, thanks to everyone's comments, I can enjoy singing.
5年間、ええ、色々ありましたが、本当に今ここに来て、ここにいてよかったなって思ってますし……
Over these 5 years, many things happened, but I'm truly glad to be here now...
……これから先ももっともっと頑張っていきたいなって思っています。
...and I want to work even harder from now on.
なので、これから先もずっと仲良くしてね。よろしくお願いします！
So, please continue to be friends with me. I look forward to it!
ええ、最後の曲はそんな気持ちを込めてアルバムの中から……ひと……ひと……ひと……ひと……
So, for the final song, with those feelings, from my album... one... one... one...
うわぁ！かっこよく終わろうと思ったのに！あ！そんな……あ、カミカミ！
Whoops! I wanted to end on a cool note! Oh man... I'm so tongue-tied!
えー、そういう気持ちを込めて
Uh, with those feelings in mind,
1曲選ばせていただきましたので、
I've chosen one song,
ぜひぜひ歌っていこうかなと思います！
so I'd like to go ahead and sing it!
では、行きますかね！
Well then, shall we go!
みんな準備はいいかな？
Is everyone ready?
最後の曲聞いてください、
Please listen to the last song,
ユメゾラ☆ファンファーレ！
Yumezora Fanfare!
約束した今日の日を
The day we promised
一生忘れない
I'll never forget it for my entire life
そんな気がした
That's how I felt
ユメゾラ☆ファンファーレ
Yumezora Fanfare
みんなありがとー！
Thank you everyone!
いくぞー！
Here we go!
あの空の向こう側
To the other side of that sky
いってみたいなんて
I'd like to try going
覗き込んだ望遠鏡
Through the telescope I peeked into
宝探しみたいだ
It's like treasure hunting
「好き」が夢を叶えるって
That "love" will make dreams come true
誰かが言ってた
Somebody said that
思い切り泣いたり
Crying as much as I want,
笑ったり
and laughing,
全速前進でしょ？
is full speed ahead, right?
明け方が星座を追い越した時
When the dawn overtook the constellations
流れる星が光った
A shooting star shone
一つだけ願うなら
If I can make just one wish
夢が叶う瞬間
The moment my dream comes true,
そばにいてくれますか？
will you stay by my side?
見に行こう
Let's go see it
ハッピーエンドのファンファーレ
The fanfare of a happy ending
キラキラの未来へ
To the sparkling future
星に負けない光と
With a light that won't lose to the stars
重なる希望 響かせて
Let the overlapping hopes resonate
涙と涙が重なって
Tears and tears overlap
ほら夜が明けるように
Like the dawn breaking
夢と夢がギュッと
Dreams and dreams, tightly
重なる瞬間を
The moment they overlap
奇跡と呼ぶんだ
We call it a miracle
着地点はいつだって
The landing point is always
キミのその笑顔
That smile of yours
遠回りしたけど出会えたんだ
We took a detour, but we met
一緒、一緒でしょ？
Together, we're together, right?
キラめく希望のメロディ描いて
Drawing a sparkling melody of hope
夢にあふれにいこう
Let's go and be filled with dreams
無数の星屑の中
In the midst of countless stardust
見つけてくれてありがとう
Thank you for finding me
大切なキミへいつの日でも
To you, who are important, every day
一番に届けよう
I'll deliver it to you first
見てて、輝きここで
Watch me shine right here
歌い続けること
That I'll continue to sing
約束するから
I promise you
ユメゾラ☆ファンファーレ Staff
Yumezora Fanfare Staff
作編曲：藤原彩豊 作詞：まつもとななみ
Comp./Arr.: Sayaka Fujiwara, Lyrics: Nanami Matsumoto
イラスト：山葵るお 動画：亜羽れいな
Illustration: Wasabi-ruo, Movie: Reina Aha
歌：ときのそら
Vocals: Tokino Sora
キミの声を聞かせてよ
Let me hear your voice
もっともっと近くで
From much, much closer
道を照らす月のように
Like the moon illuminating the path
ずっとずっとずっと、
Always, always, always...
みんな大好き！
I love you all!
ハッピーエンドのファンファーレ
The fanfare of a happy ending
虹に願いを込めて
Putting a wish into the rainbow
見たことのない世界へ
To a world we've never seen
ステップ踏んで飛び出そう
Let's step out and jump out
笑顔と笑顔が重なって
Smile and smile overlap
虹がかかるように
Like a rainbow forming
夢と夢がギュッと
Dreams and dreams, tightly
重なる瞬間を
The moment they overlap
奇跡と呼ぶんだ
We call it a miracle
いこうよ、ユメゾラの向こうへ
Let's go, beyond the dream sky
本日は、本当に本当にありがとうございましたー！
Thank you so much for today!
そして最後に、ここでみなさんにお知らせがあります。
And finally, I have an announcement for everyone here.
先ほど18時には発表になってるんですけど、なんと！
It was already announced at 6:00 PM, but...
ときのそら 5th Anniversary Live 開催決定！
Tokino Sora 5th Anniversary Live confirmed!
ときのそら 5th Anniversary Live
Tokino Sora 5th Anniversary Live...
「宇宙(そら)と時空(とき)のミルキーウェイ」ワンマンライブの開催が
..."Milky Way of Space (Sora) and Time (Toki)" solo live...
決定しました！ありがとうございます！
...has been confirmed! Thank you so much!
えー、2022年11月19日土曜日、
Um, on Saturday, November 19, 2022,
えー、東京・かつしかシンフォニーヒルズ モーツァルトホールにて、
at the Katsushika Symphony Hills Mozart Hall in Tokyo,
えー、オンラインはいつものSPWNさんで、えー、やらせていただきます。
the online stream will be held on the usual SPWN.
今回も昼と夜の2公演です。
There will be two performances, afternoon and evening, this time as well.
終演後にアフタートークもありますよ。
There will also be an after-talk after the show.
チケットの発売はもう始まってます。
Ticket sales have already started.
そしてなんと、初めての生バンドでのライブとなります！
And surprisingly, it will be my first live with a live band!
みんなと一緒に素敵な思い出が作りたい。
I want to make wonderful memories with everyone.
ぜひぜひみんな遊びに来てね！
Please, everyone, come and visit!
そして、そして！
And, and!
5周年記念特別番組「ときのかけはし」
5th Anniversary Special Program "Toki no Kakehashi"
このあと、ホロライブプロダクション5周年記念特番「ときのかけはし」が
Following this, the Hololive Production 5th Anniversary Special Program "Toki no Kakehashi"...
放送されます。
...will be broadcast.
私も出演して谷郷社長とお話ししておりますので、ぜひご覧ください。
I will be appearing and talking with CEO Tanigo, so please check it out.
よろしくお願いします！
Please support us!
ありがとみんなー！
Thank you everyone!